hoisthospitality.com 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy - Hoist Group

In order to provide our customers with information, news and promotions such as event invitations, Hoist Group needs to process certain personal data. All our legal obligations are taken very seriously and we will always process your data with the protection of your privacy as our main priority. This means that we strive after not storing more data than what is necessary to carry out the purposes of the processing and to not store the data for longer than needed.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and process your personal data. Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable person, for example names, other contact details and identification numbers. Processing of personal data means any action taken on personal data such as, for example, collection, storage, use and transfer of personal data. The policy also explains what legal rights you have related to our processing of your personal data.

Please read this information thoroughly and contact us on [info@hoistgroup.com](mailto:info@hoistgroup.com) if you have any questions related to our data processing. Hoist AB, VAT: SE556460-231501, Box 6074, SE-171 06 Solna, Sweden is the controller responsible for the processing carried out according to this policy.

### What personal data do we collect for marketing purpose and why?

We collect the following data about you:

  * E-mail address
  * Name
  * Title
  * Company
  * Company postal address
  * Phone number
  * In relation to events, pictures in which you may be visible

We collect the above data in order to be able to contact you with information regarding our services as well as events and other news related to Hoist Group. The legal basis for our processing of data is our mutual legitimate interests in exchanging information, sharing invitations to and material from events, and similar. Hoist Group considers the processing of personal data necessary for carrying out such activities and that your right to privacy does not outweigh our interest in carrying out the activities mentioned in this context. Also, pictures taken on events and similar may be used in our marketing. For such personal data processing, we have obtained your consent.

### How and from where do we collect personal data and how long do we store it?

We collect personal data either by storing it following your contact with us, for example when you sign up for any of our events or newsletters.

We store your data for as long as it is necessary for the mentioned purposes, or until you decline to receive further communication from us.

### With whom do we share personal data?

Hoist Group will never share your personal data with any third parties for marketing purpose.

### What are your rights?

You have the right to request access to the personal data that we process regarding you. You will then obtain information such as which personal data regarding you that we process, the purposes of our processing, to which (if any) the personal data will or have been disclosed and for which time period the personal data will be stored.

You also have the right to request rectification or erasure of data, or to request that we restrict our processing of data. Regarding processing where the legal basis is consent, you also have the right to at any time revoke your consent. To request your data or correspond with Hoist Group about your data please e-mail us: [dpo@hoistgroup.com](mailto:dpo@hoistgroup.com)

You also have the possibility to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority in Sweden, Datainspektionen, see link for contact details: <http://www.datainspektionen.se/in-english/contact-us/>.
